{
    "subject": "resource/Yosi_Piamenta",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Jerusalem",
    "human_readable": "Yosi Piamenta was born in Jerusalem.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8939895629882812,
            "question": "Where was Yosi Piamenta born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8449747562408447,
            "question": "When was Yosi Piamenta born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6086975336074829,
            "question": "What nationality is Yosi Piamenta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40504708886146545,
            "question": "Is Yosi Piamenta known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37102124094963074,
            "question": "Do you know any other famous people born in Jerusalem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2201613336801529,
            "question": "What is Jerusalem known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1283424347639084,
            "question": "Is there a famous musical tradition associated with Jerusalem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12107823044061661,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Jerusalem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11980435252189636,
            "question": "What is the cultural significance of Jerusalem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07915527373552322,
            "question": "Who are some other prominent musicians from Israel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Yosi Piamenta was born in Jerusalem.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3450_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the cultural significance of Jerusalem?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3450_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Jerusalem?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3450_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a famous musical tradition associated with Jerusalem?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3450_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3450_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple that Yosi Piamenta was born in Jerusalem. All five files mention that Piamenta was born in Jerusalem, Israel, specifically mentioning his birth year as 1951."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple mentions of Yosi Piamenta being born in Jerusalem, Israel, in 1951. Therefore, the statement \"Yosi Piamenta was born in Jerusalem\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}